Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your work!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Hallo! Stee, this time I am joined by Momohime Seino of Beyondz Rain Forest River Sea and Kirara Yonemura of Tea Horse.
This time, we will be presenting with these two, so please stay with us until the end.
We are both the same age, and we are trainees in the same class.
We have known each other for 8 years.
Oh my God.
What do you think?
I've been checking your Instagram often, but Momohime dyes her hair, does her makeup and nails, and I think it really shows her personality.
Thank you very much.
I think it's really cool that Momohime's color comes out so much.
Kirara is a member of a separate group, the Tea Horses,
I feel that Kirara is a great leader among the tea ceremony horses.
I think she is an amazing person, and we have both grown up a lot.
Yes, eight years. I joined the group when I was in the 5th grade of elementary school or something.
You have grown up, haven't you?
Yes, we have. So, BEYOND is preparing for concerts and live performances in different formats.
BIOPHONIC2 will be held on April 6 at Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space and on May 10 at Kobe International Conference Hall.
BEYOND LIVE TOUR2024 SPRING PERSONALITY will start on April 7 with a concert in Hiroshima.
Yes, BIOPHONIC 2 is a concert with full orchestral arrangement,
It is really a different atmosphere from the usual BEYOND concert, and it is more tense, so this time too,
I hope to deliver BEYOND with care and attention.
I hope to deliver BEYOND carefully and carefully this time.
zone and my emic are aligned, and I continue to tileA.
It rides to OWatchTour, and I think it is already quite enough,
This component puki puki read Devika so far umes coiese
I would like to show you the colors of the
Elizabeth army 2 minutes ente quite a popular group, oh my, there's so much to see and do with everyone.
The attribute is Yamamotozaka.
We are going to visit many places in Japan, so we are going to have a lot of fun with the audience at each place.
I hope to have a lot of fun with the audience at each location.
I hope to make good memories with the audience at each stop.
Just before the tour
March 30th and 31st, Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 will be held.
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 will be held on March 30 and 31.
What do you think of Hinafes?
Hinafes, yes!
I, Yonemura, won the shuffle trio!
That's right.
That's right, Momohime's group.
Hirai and Shiori Nishida of the Beyoncé group.
Amazing, isn't it?
They're two amazing performers.
No, no, no, it's amazing.
But I can't stop being nervous.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Please watch it.
Thank you very much for your warm encore.
Thank you very much.
Here we are.
Morning Musume。 I have an announcement.
What a surprise!
The final show of the tour has been decided!
The venue is
Nippon Budokan
It will be on the 27th of May!
And you know what?
The final date of our concert
The final of our concert has been decided
We have to make it more and more exciting
We're going to have a concert.
We're going to keep going until the end.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you for watching!
Protecting you, protecting the stars, living today, connecting to tomorrow
Someday, a gentle era that will never be forgotten will envelop this whole world.
I will protect you, I will protect the stars, I will protect the stars, I will connect you to tomorrow
That thing in memory of you...
Even if I lose it, will I keep it in my heart?
Every sunset makes me cry
I'm done blaming someone else
♪ Dreams are the flip side of loneliness
Now, if you're aiming for the highest glory and pride
With you, with you, with you flying With you dreaming, with you sweating
Someday, love's voice will be good The age of freedom will blow all the bad things away
A time that wants to make you right
You're the one on the edge, living on the edge, but you've made it through without breaking your heart
The smell of the city, the fact that I couldn't get used to it, the fact that it was fading away...
The latest is no longer the latest
Well, you can't let your regrets get in the way of your happiness.
It's great to be alive
Ah, protecting you, protecting the stars
Living for today
♪ And we'll make it to tomorrow
Someday we won't have to fight
A kinder, gentler time
Will envelop this whole world
Your smile makes the colors
Love makes the oceans of the sea
Love makes the oceans of ocean
Your smile makes the colors
From you, I have one more dream
With you, with your sweat
Someday I won't change I won't change
When you're free
Wipe all the bad things away
I'm not gonna make you sad.
I'm sure you'll be the same as you always were
Ions, Rain Forest, Kianomohime on the river
and Kirara Yanagimura of Ocha-no-Ma, Haloste.
From here, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
I'll do my best.
Okay, I'll get right to it.
Kirara will turn 20 years old in a little over a month.
What is the first thing that comes to your mind when you hear the word "20s"?
Adulthood.
Kirara's hobby is solo karaoke.
Which song from Ocha no Oma would you recommend for solo karaoke?
Rabirabi
What are you personally interested in now?
Pilates
Who is a junior student you are interested in right now?
Sara Kono, a trainee from Halo Pro.
What has changed the most between your debut and now?
I've become stronger.
Yes, thank you very much.
A lot has happened, but...
Um, what song would you recommend for solo karaoke?
Yes.
Rabbi David?
It's Rabbi David.
I know it sounds difficult...
Rabidabi is very difficult.
But there's a tikiyan at the beginning and in between the songs.
Chikiyan.
There's a dialogue or a key part in the song.
I was wondering how the fans do it in karaoke.
I see.
I have to say something.
The lyrics are displayed.
You're right.
You have to say it properly?
Yes, I have to say it in a sexy, breathy way.
Even if you do it alone.
Yes, I'd like you to try it at karaoke by yourself.
Yes, that would be nice.
And the younger girl I'm interested in right now...
Kaa-chan Soara?
Yes, Soara. She's a trainee.
Isn't she cute?
So cute!
She's really cute.
I probably shouldn't stare at her, but when we're backstage together, I unconsciously do.
So I keep looking at her in the mirror while we're eating, and it's a little disgusting.
I don't like it. It's a little suspicious. I know, but it's cute.
He's so cute. I love his face. He's so cute. Please be nice to him.
Please be nice to her.
Hallo! Sta!
Ghetto!
Shall we dance?
Summer
Life!
Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Let's drink tea tea tea tea tea tea tea tea tea
Our
Tea for Tea! First album Channel 1 now on sale!
This is not right!
My heart can't overflow!
Tears of Heroine
Declaration of getting off
Topinorei
My life End point
It doesn't matter what yet
Haloste
Next, I would like to ask Momohime a question.
Okay, here we go.
What is the first thing that comes to mind when you hear the word "spring"?
Pollen.
The Lyons live tour starts on April 7.
What is Momohime's must-have for the tour?
Powder
Theater girls' club beauty spy next week on the 27th
Blu-ray release of The Missing Attache Case
What do you recommend people watch over and over again?
The scene where I play Kay and she steals the jewelry.
What is your favorite part of the hair and makeup?
My eyelashes.
August marks the 5th anniversary of your major label debut!
How do you want to spend this anniversary?
I want to spend it with my fans.
Thank you very much.
I've heard a lot about you.
Must-haves for the tour?
Powder.
I have three kinds of powder.
I use three different kinds of powder for my face.
I have what's called combination skin.
I have combination skin, which means that some parts of my skin collapse due to sebum and some parts are dry.
I use two kinds of powder for that.
I also use a powder that is good for my skin.
Where I want to apply it thinly
I want to apply it thinly where I want to apply it thinly
I'm trying to separate them.
I can't do a show without it.
I can't do the show without it.
And the thing that caught my attention?
The hair and makeup.
Yes, that's right.
I answered "eyelashes.
I have lower eyelashes.
They're really long.
Really?
I'm looking at them from the side.
My top lashes are really long, too.
But they're just as long.
Really?
These are all my own eyelashes.
But if you work hard and apply a lot of serum...
They'll grow longer.
It's amazing.
Try to grow them out!
By the way, what is the point of hair?
What is the point of hair?
I don't know...
Do the hair you like.
I see.
It doesn't have to be chopped hair.
I'm going to try tying a knot here and there.
My point is to be proactive and adventurous.
I see.
Let's just do what we want without worrying about what other people think.
Let's just do what we want to do.
Just do what you want to do.
That's right.
That's what I mean.
That's what I like about life.
Yes, sir.
So...
Hello! We'll be back with more after this.
Thank you for watching!
This is Miyavi Nakiyaki. Here we go. Hello Kitchen. This time, we have a member here.
This is Anzurumu Shimoita Nikkyo. I will do my best in cooking. Let's do our best. Please give me your best. Yes, thank you very much. What did you make this time?
I'm going to make a meat bun and a bean-jam bun. That's good. It's my first time. I'm really looking forward to it. Here are the ingredients.
So, Yukiho, do you cook? I do a little bit. Are you interested in cooking?
Yes, I am. I would like to, but I don't know where to start.
Let's have fun cooking together today. Let's work hard. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
What would you like to do first?
First of all, I would like to make the skin around it.
Okay, let's make it.
140 grams of flour, 60 grams of flour, and up to 2 pinches of salt.
I brought dry yeast.
I've brought the dry yeast, and it's sleeping.
Sleeping?
Sleeping.
Oh, my God.
I have to wake him up.
Wake him up.
To wake him up, you need warm water.
Heh...
Mix with hot water
Mix with hot water, yes.
4 grams.
Put 4 grams in.
Yes, sir.
I'll wake him up.
Yes, please.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
Mix it. Leave it a little bit. It's okay.
And put the sugar over here.
Yes, 10 grams of sugar.
Put 10 grams.
Okay. - Okay.
And put it in the middle.
Then, you know, make a little hollow in the middle.
And then, you know, divide it into about three times.
Put it in about three times.
Oh, the way we like it.
Hmm?
Your favorite?
Yes, I like to put it in like this.
What? Why?
It's more fun.
Instead of doing it all at once?
Yes, I do.
It's like when you make monja.
Yes, that's right.
You put the ingredients in a little at a time.
It's not easy to cook.
Everyone is busy.
That's right.
But the other day, I made my own pork miso soup.
Oh, I see.
Yes, I did.
No, I didn't.
What's that? You made it because you wanted to eat pork miso soup?
Yes, I did.
huh?
I was going to make miso soup at first, but then I thought, "Pork miso soup...
But it turned out like that.
It turned out like Pork miso soup.
Oh, I just did it...
Oh, I get it.
I wanted to put something in it, like chikuwa or kamaboko or...
Leeks, sweet potatoes...
Oh, you put a lot of things in there!
I put carrots and mushrooms...
This looks amazing.
It looks delicious.
All-stars!
This is not miso soup.
It has a lot of ingredients
Yes, it is.
It's for soup.
10g of oil
The oil gives it luster.
In this.
And here's the powder.
You take out all the powder.
It's like cleaning it out.
Scrape off all of it.
Yes, sir.
And when you've removed it, put it out here.
This is still rough, isn't it?
It will be shiny now.
Wow!
I'd like you to knead it until then.
Okay, I'll take you to the esthetician's corner in a minute.
Oh, don't be gentle.
It has to be intense.
It's like you're swelling up.
Yes, yes, yes.
Gut it, please.
I heard this customer has a lot of swelling.
I'd like to massage and stretch it out now.
Like this.
That's right.
Speedy.
It's like putting your weight on it.
That's how the gluten is formed.
It's so soft and fluffy.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
You can just put it on now.
Okay, let's go now.
Ha-ha-ha. That's fun.
I'm going to go talk to him.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yukiho, what are you good at?
Good at what?
I'm fine with whatever I'm good at.
But let's just say I can sign.
Oh, sign language.
Sign language.
Can you sign? Sign language
No, I don't sign at all.
I'm sorry.
Like, hello?
Oh, yes, that's right.
Yes, that's right.
By the way, a bun or something?
Was it bean-paste buns today?
Today, yes.
"Niku-man-man"?
There's actually a sign language for meat buns.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Grab it like this, circle it like this, and put a bun like this.
A bun.
Ew!
So cute!
manjuu (steamed bun with meat filling)
yes
A bun with meat.
Yes, sir.
Yes!
steamed meat bun
I wonder how they're going to make the steamed meat buns today.
Oh, how did I do it?
I'll make it.
Huh?
Like that.
I'll make it.
After we make it
And this
Swelling is gone
Swelling went down, didn't it?
It's gone down, isn't it?
The bumps have gone down.
I'm happy for you.
Yes, sir.
And this girl...
Wrap it up.
Yes, sir.
Wrap her up.
You might want to double wrap it.
It's hard to wrap with this powder.
Yes, yes.
It's slippery.
Okay.
And now, the third one.
O Poils
Ou
Ou Yes
Cool.
Yes, yes, yes.
So...
About 5 times
Yes.
About this much.
Forty percent.
The heat is freshly turned on.
That's about right.
Thank you very much.
I'll have them wait for you.
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
While the dough is lying down, I'd like to make the filling, the seeds. The seeds of the buns.
They are called seeds, right? They are kneaded with only minced meat and salt.
What do people usually call you, Yukiho-chan? People call me Yukiho.
Oh, they call me Yupyon.
Yupyon.
Cute.
I like rabbits, so I'm like "yup, yup, yup.
Like a "yip-yip"?
But it fits.
It's cute.
Is that the nickname the members gave you?
Yes, they did.
Heh.
Not at school, then?
At school, we are usually Yuki-chan and Yukiho-chan.
Yuki-chan and Yukiho-chan?
They call me that after things and stuff, too.
Nicknames?
Yes.
By the members?
Oh, no. By your friends?
They call me Shimo-san.
Shimo-san. Suddenly you seem a little bitter.
He's austere. It's like he's a big guy.
Really, really. Suddenly.
It's "Yukiho" on the bottom board, isn't it?
That's an unusual name.
That's unusual.
It's the first time.
That's something.
But when it gets sticky, it'll be fine.
Moist.
Yes, it's moist. Then, the only part of the day where you use a knife.
Yes. We're going to use green onions.
Please keep the spacing even.
Okay.
Cut them in the same direction one more time.
Then it becomes a backflip.
This is a cross, so if you cut from this side like this...
Oh! Oh, wow!
Wow, that's great.
I'm learning.
Oh, is that something?
Just a little.
I'll just drop it right here.
I'll hold it.
That's what I'm talking about.
Here's 30 grams.
30 grams.
A fine one.
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's weigh out the seasonings.
10 grams of soy sauce.
10 grams.
Okay. 10 grams of oyster sauce.
Also 10 grams of oyster sauce.
Sesame oil.
Yes.
That's a lot of oil. Like this.
I guess you feel like you're cooking the moment you put it in like this.
Ah, the moment of mixing.
The moment of mixing.
The moment you put it in.
You use both hands for this, too.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
Yes, that's right.
Mix like this.
Yeah.
You change this bowl, you know, and mix it like that.
I see.
That's right.
Yes. When it's mixed, it's OK.
Once mixed, divide into thirds.
That's right.
Yes.
Yes. When it's all round, put three pieces here.
Just lightly.
Okay.
They're cute.
Yes.
Yes, I'll give you some bean-jam seeds then. Yes.
5:30, 150 grams, ground black sesame seeds, sesame oil, here. Sesame oil.
Sesame. Sesame oil here, too. Sesame oil here, too.
Surprising. I guess it's time for a taste test, right? Huh?
Well, please go ahead. I've already made and eaten it before. I've already made it and eaten it.
Bon appétit.
Yes, it's good.
It's a bit authentic, isn't it?
It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
It's a little different from the one at the convenience store, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's fragrant.
The sesame is very strong.
The flavor comes out.
Then, you put it in three pieces, just like before.
Yes.
This time,
That's all.
It's all done.
Yes, we've already done that.
The seeds are already finished,
Is it difficult to wrap the head?
Yes, it's difficult.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Well, let's work on that next time.
Okay.
Looking forward to it.
Is it ready?
Yeah, I'm good. It's ready, it's ready, it's ready.
It's ready.
Yeah, it's ready. Now, if you'd just give it a little more of a tug on the top.
You're a prettier kappa than your teacher.
Really?
Bon appétit.
Wow.
It looks delicious.
I'm really looking forward to the finished product. I'm looking forward to it.
Do you cook? Recently, I made Hayashi Rice. Hayashi Rice?
Isn't it amazing? It's amazing. It's amazing. What? But it's just roux. Roux. But it's still amazing. But it's so easy.
I see. That's great. Thankfully, it's a little bit easy to make. You can make it. You just pour in water, pour in the roux, and add the ingredients,
I just put in the water, the roux, and the ingredients ahead of time. Wow, that's great. You made it? I make everything at once.
Even the roux. Because you never know when you're going to make it again, and it would be a waste if you wait. I have the desire to do it.
I made it all at once, and it was for eight people. You made 8 servings? You mean you made it all at once? Yes. I made 8 servings at once,
I had to eat it all by myself. So I ate all of it with Hayashi Rice for breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Wow. Don't you ever get tired of it?
I never got tired of it. I see. You know, I often say to myself, "I'm going to eat beef bowl for the rest of my life. I can eat beef bowl for the rest of my life or hamburger steak for the rest of my life. I can eat whatever I want for the rest of my life.
I can probably eat either one. Wow. I can probably eat all kinds of food. That's amazing.
Forever, because that's something. I see. It might have been two days or something. I see.
Well, but wow. It was so delicious. I want to make it. On the other hand, is there anything you want to make? I want to make Thai food now.
Thai food sounds difficult. Yes, I love Thai food, like Pad Thai, and green curry. Green curry is called "Genki Aowan" in Thai. Genki Aowan.
Yes, Genki Aowan means sweet white curry. Green Curry is like green curry in Japan.
So, Thai people put white coconut milk in it, which is why it is called "white sweet". Wow. So, you have to follow the order.
I would like to embody the reason why it becomes that "energetic" green curry myself. Wow, that's great. It fits. Green curry is green?
You've never had it? You've never had it? No, I haven't. You don't want to eat it? I want to. Let's go eat it together sometime. Let's go, let's go, let's go. I want to go.
A presentation of lyrics that touched my heart!
In this corner, we will present lyrics from Hello! Project songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics.
Project songs and talk about their charms. Project songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Kotoka, will be presenting.
Here it is.
Belin!
You're not the real you if you're reduced to a smiling, laughing, silly woman.
It's for being Ms. Bono's Independent Girl Independent Girl!
It's cool!
The lyrics of this song are not so much kind as they are really strong.
So there are some parts that really hit me hard for a moment.
I think the part about the smiling, silly girl is not about a girl who is happy and having a good time, but about a girl who is just trying to be a friend to someone who is smiling and having a good time.
I'm not saying that a girl who is happy and smiling is stupid, but that a girl who is smiling and laughing is stupid because she matches her friends' and loved ones' tastes.
She goes along with her friends, her significant other, her tastes...
Like, you're not yourself, you're not the real you.
That's not the real me.
There is something like that.
I think the lyrics are saying, "That's not you, that's not the real you.
I think that's what the lyrics are saying.
I like it.
Yeah, it's cool!
It's cool! This song is really cool!
I sometimes think that I want to be an independent girl, or an independent woman.
I think this song has a lot of that in it.
I like it too!
I don't mean to say that I'm an independent girl, but...
I'm not saying I'm an independent girl, but to be an independent girl, it's a corner for me to be a strong girl.
You know...
I think we're connected.
I think we're all connected, and there's a sense of being subservient to each other.
You talk behind my back, you talk bad about me...
It's like you're the strong one, or you're the one who's taking responsibility for yourself.
I don't think there is no such thing as a person who can take responsibility for others.
So I think it's about being a girl who doesn't get hung up on that kind of thing.
I think about it a lot.
I see...
Yes, this is...
Of course, I'm trying to convey this in the lyrics, but...
If there were this Ms. A and Ms. B
Mr. A understands Mr. B, right?
He knows that you are not the one smiling like that
I think it's great that Mr. A understands that.
That's true.
If you think about it...
Yes, there are people who are watching us.
I think a lot of people will be encouraged by this song.
That's true.
It's good.
Okay.
Well, that's how I'd like to end.
That was the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much!
BEYOND Ame no Mari This is Halo! STE!
As I mentioned in the opening, we are the same age and the same trainee.
We have been friends for more than 8 years now.
Surprise!
What a surprise!
I've made a sketchbook of our first impressions of each other, and I'd like to present it to you at the same time.
I'd like to share them with you at the same time.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
Ta-da!
I'll go first... and tell you that I was a professional...
I was just a 5th grade elementary school student from Aichi Prefecture, and I didn't even know where to go, and when I was taken to that room, I didn't know what to do or who to talk to or anything.
I didn't know what to do in that room, I didn't know who to talk to, I didn't know anything.
I didn't know what to do in that room, I didn't know who to talk to, I didn't know what to do, and I didn't know what to do, and I didn't know what to do.
And she's all like, "Tetsuro," and she's all smiles, and she introduces herself, and she's like, "Please call me Green.
No, no, no, that's the great thing about it, too.
And he taught me everything perfectly, and he didn't even break into a smile, and I thought, "Well, he's got the same motive as me, so maybe he's a little bit jealous of me, or something.
I wondered if he was a little tense.
I was like, "Oh, my God, you're so nice, you're so nice, you're so nice.
Thank you, that was an ageless microphone.
I'm a pro now, but I think I was a pro back then.
But now I'm starting to show a part of myself that's my own, so yeah, I guess...
In the sense that I don't... there's a lot of things I don't do right.
And the first impression of the fliter killer that hides me... I say I didn't know what I was doing, but it's my first day as a trainee, and it's also my first day on set.
When I went to the office on the first day of shooting, I was really scared of the manager at the time, but I was so nervous that I went to talk to him, but he was so excited.
I was so nervous and I went to talk to the manager, but Killer was so excited and he just spun me around in front of the manager.
You know, Geсти.
I don't think so.
Momohime is more amazing.
Momohime is huge!
We've talked a bit, but how has your impression of her changed over the past 8 years?
But I thought she was a professional at first and then gradually I started to see a little bit of her human side and we became very close so I think that part has changed a lot.
I think it changed from my first impression.
I think so... I think Kirara hasn't changed much.
I think that if we had met 8 or 7 years ago today, she would probably have been like this, and I'm sure that's true.
I mean, we're probably the same, but the aspects that we show to each other, we've both grown into this.
We have!
Thank you for watching!
Finally, I stepped on it, and it was a treasure.
I'm sick of everything.
A tragic sacrifice
Lazy, lazy, spoiled doggie
All this life
I've got this thing on my cheek
It's like I'm scolding you
Only the timing of the sweets of the sweets of the sweets of the sweets of the sweets of the sweets of the sweets of the sweets of the sweets of the sweets
It's about time, spring is sad
Get your pride back
I don't know what it's like
I'm having a hard time repeating myself
Say bye bye bye
Get your pride back
If it's gonna stand up someday, what's more
Rafira's
A wide line of descent
There will be a replacement for you
I'll take mine
Don't make me love you
The world is a wide descending line of tears
I don't deserve to be miserable
I'll fight over every last one of you
Let's seize this glorious summer day
Subtitle Kiminomiya
yeah
I rubbed it in that you're not good at it, and sent it away
2zop for workin'
A little bit out of your way Invincible Walking
Let's go up, let's go where we're going
Take it back, pride.
Just like that.
I repeat, it's hard.
Poly Paris Passion
Take it back, take it back, take it back Pride
If you're gonna stand up someday, it's not now or now
I'll pick up the tears and declare that I'm going down
I'm sorry you don't see enough
You're a sad little girl, aren't you?
You have to give it to him
♪ Pick up the tears and declare that you're getting off
I'm not going to skip out on any of the pretenses
♪ I'm not gonna skip a beat ♪ ♪ I'm gonna be happy ♪
♪ Let's grab it, Baby
It's a gorgeous summer day
Say where?
Shout, Shout, Shout!
Shout!
Super shine you were born with
Now it's time! Let's go!
Now it's time!
Tearful heroine on the way down
There's always someone to take your place, right?
I'm the one
I have to love you.
Tears of a heroine on the line of descent
I don't deserve to be miserable
Dodging the spotlight
I'll grab the spotlight! It's a glamorous story
Wow wow wow wow
Wow wow wow wow wow
Yeah!
Are you trying too hard? Try relaxing your shoulders
Beyond Rain Forest, Momohime Seino of Kawakami
and Kirara Yonemura of Ochanomaha, presenting Haloste.
It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
On March 30th and 31st at Makuhari Messe
Hinafest 2024 will be held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31!
And also on March 30 and 31 at Makuhari Messe
Carbon Neutral 2024 by Satoyama Umi Movement will also be held on March 30 and 31 at Makuhari Messe.
by Satosanzanoumi Movement will also be held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.
This event has become an annual event for us.
We look forward to seeing you all there!
And Hello Project 25th Anniversary Concert
Theme of Hello All for One & One for All
Blu-ray will be released today!
This concert was held to celebrate the 25th anniversary of Hello Project.
25th anniversary concert.
This concert is really packed with a lot of contents.
Please check it out!
We also had the pleasure of performing last year's
Theater Girls Club Biospy
The Blu-ray of "The Missing Attache Case" will be released
will be released next week on March 27th!
I told you a little bit about it earlier.
I play the role of Kay, right?
I play Kay, who steals jewelry.
I'm playing Kay, and she's a little bit tricky.
We're all switching attache cases and fighting with a lot of action.
The fights are very action-packed.
Please watch it again and again!
And Biophonic 2 will be performed on April 6 at the Tokyo Metropolitan Theatre
And on May 10th at the Kobe International Conference Center
on April 6 at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space and on May 10 at the Kobe International Conference Center.
Please come and enjoy it as well!
And Beyonce Live Tour 2024 Spring
personality will start on April 7 in Hiroshima!
We will bring you Beyonce's passionate performance!
We hope you will join us!
And what about the Beyonce's?
They will perform at Japan Jam 2024 on May 4!
Thank you very much!
It has been my dream to perform at a music festival
It was so much fun!
I'm very happy!
I will do my best to leave my mark on the world!
And the Ocha-no-Oma
Ocha-no-Oma Live Tour 2024
Our hometown is Japan!
The tour will start on April 7th in Osaka!
We will be touring all over the country.
We are going to play all over the country this time, too.
Please check it out!
And on March 24th, the tea time!
Kataria Presents Pop Culture Live!
And on March 28th
NIG Fest 2024
And on May 1st
Lifestyle withDOX2024
Live event
Nearly Equal Joy x Ocha no Oma
We will be performing
This is a two-for-one event with Nearly Equal Joy
This is a two-member event with Nearly Equal Joy
We are all looking forward to it!
Please come and join us!
Please come and join us! Project members will be performing at Halo! Project members
Project members!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time we have
BEYONDZ: The Rain Forest, Kawakami's Kiru no Momohime and
and Kirara Yonemura, the tea lady!
Good bye.